const questions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'ChakraUi',
      answer:
        "Chakra UI is a simple, modular and accessible component library that helps me to build full-responsive blocks pretty fast. I use it as a combination of Sass. ",
    },
  
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'ExpressJs',
      answer:
        "Express.js is a back end web application framework that helps me to easily connect to a database and make requests. It is fast, robust and secure.",
    },
  
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "MetaMask",
      answer:
        'Metamask is available as a browser extension and equips you with a key vault, secure login, decentralized wallet and crypto exchange. It may be seen as the best Paypal alternative on the current market.',
    },
  
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "MongoDB",
      answer:
        'MongoDB is the easiest way to deploy, operate and scale a database in the cloud. It helps me to create a database fast.',
    },
  
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "NextJs",
      answer:
        "NextJs is React framework. It gives the best features for production. It is the most advanced, fast and easy-to-deploy web application builder. It is also the best framework for pages management and SEO solutions.",
    },
  
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "NodeJs",
      answer:
        'NodeJs is a server-side programming language. I use to construct servers and connect to database.',
    },
  
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Sanity.io",
      answer:
        "Sanity is the platform for structured content. It helps me to quickly create product database, categories, description, etc. It is also very useful as client-side CMS (content management system).",
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Sass",
        answer:
          "Sass is the most mature, stable, and powerful professional web design language. It helps me to write clean and easy to reuse code.",
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: "Solidity",
        answer:
          "Solidity is an object-oriented, high-level language for implementing smart contracts on the blockchain. I use it to create proof of authenticity for your art: aka NFT (non-fungible token: a unique digital identifier that cannot be copied, substituted, or subdivided, and that is recorded in a blockchain.",
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: "Stripe.io",
        answer:
          "Stripe is platform that makes online payment easy, fast and secured. The most advanced tool for any kind of online-business so far.",
      },
  ]
  
  export default questions